content,annotations
"In This Article: (Bloomberg) -- Investors willing to go against the market in the coming months should consider selling US technology stocks and private credit, while boosting holdings in China, according to the head of Norway’s $1.8 trillion sovereign wealth fund. Most Read from Bloomberg Texas HOA Charged With Discrimination for Banning Section 8 Renters How Sanctuary Cities Are Preparing for Another Showdown With Trump Donations to LA Fire Victims Rise Past $200 Million Mark NY’s Hochul Calls for Law Banning Cell Phone Use in Schools LA Schools Wrecked by Fires Plead on GoFundMe for Help to Reopen “The best thing to do is always to do the opposite of everybody else,” Nicolai Tangen said in an interview with David Rubenstein at Bloomberg House during the World Economic Forum in Davos on Wednesday. “What will that be today? Well, if you were to do the opposite of everybody else, it would be to sell the US tech stocks, buy China, sell private credit, just buy stuff that is out of fashion.” He acknowledged that’s “very, very tough to do because if you are contrarian and you are different from your benchmarks and so on, there will be periods where you underperform and everybody is going to question your sanity,” the executive said. The executive joined Norges Bank Investment Management — the official manager of the fund — in September 2020 from AKO Capital, the hedge fund he founded in 2005. During his tenure, Tangen has urged his traders to think long-term and warned that inflation is likely to continue to weigh on returns in the coming years. While Tangen has encouraged his staff to be contrarian, he stopped short of saying whether the fund was reducing holdings in US technology stocks and adding China. NBIM is due to report key financial figures for 2024 on Jan. 29. A second administration of President Donald Trump that reduces regulation and drives growth may be “really good for our companies in America,” the executive said, while tariffs will negatively affect Europe. “There is a big question whether the policies will be inflationary, which would be bad news in the in the longer term,” Tangen said, citing tighter labor markets and tariffs as factors that may drive up costs. “There could be a moment where — given the high level of government debt — investors suddenly decide, ‘we want a much higher coupon to lend to governments.’ So you could see a step up in interest rates, which could be negative for financial markets.” Investors should be on the lookout for rising yields on long-term debt in the US, as the best indicator for inflationary pressure, the executive said on a panel discussing the trajectory for interest rates later in the morning. “It’s the stuff you cannot model which really derails markets,” he said, such as the financial crisis, the Covid-19 pandemic and the 2011 earthquake and tsunami in Japan. “They come about every so often and there will be another one coming up.” The oil fund, as it is known at home, is the world’s biggest single owner of public equities, with shares in almost 9,000 companies globally. It was established in the 1990s to invest Norway’s petroleum wealth and is largely an index-tracker, working according to a strict mandate from the country’s Finance Ministry. With Tangen at the helm, NBIM has taken a stronger stance on environmental, social and governance issues. Efforts have included disclosing voting intentions ahead of annual general meetings and sitting on advisory boards for international standard setting bodies. That focus isn’t going away despite a backlash in the US, Tangen said on Wednesday. The executive has also sought to boost NBIM’s profile at home and abroad through a communications blitz that includes hosting a regular podcast. Tangen, 58, is not above poking fun at himself, seeking to use his profile and popularity to attract young talent to the fund. Born in the southern Norwegian city of Kristiansand, the CEO began his career in the Norwegian military, where he studied Russian with the intelligence services. He went on to study finance at Wharton School, followed by a career in London that included a stint at Egerton Capital. And avid sailor, chef and art collector, Tangen also holds masters degrees in art history and social psychology. During Wednesday’s interview, Tangen said he prioritizes learning over money and that stubbornness and agility are key characteristics for a good investor. “When things change, you have to change your mind. And that’s the rarest combination in investment management,” the executive said. He said Wednesday that he wants to continue in the post when his current five-year stint expires in September, adding that he does not foresee going into politics or moving on to another money-managing role once he wraps up his time at the fund. “I’d love to go back to university at some stage, do a degree,” he said. “That’s how you measure happiness, by how much you have learned.” The executive is among those who have signed the Giving Pledge, which commits signatories to passing on the majority of their wealth to philanthropy during their lifetimes or in their wills. “I’ve got enough money to buy food and shoes,” he said. For the full interview with Norges Bank Investment Management CEO Nicolai Tangen, watch “The David Rubenstein Show: Peer to Peer Conversations” on Bloomberg Television on Wednesday, Feb. 19 at 9:00 p.m. in New York and Thursday, Feb. 20 at 6:00 p.m. in London. --With assistance from Federica Romaniello and Stephen Treloar. (Updates with additional comments starting in eighth paragraph.) Most Read from Bloomberg Businessweek How Kendrick Lamar Turned Beef With Drake Into Music Superstardom Walgreens Replaced Fridge Doors With Smart Screens. It’s Now a $200 Million Fiasco Elon Musk’s Inaugural Highs (and Lows) Giant Batteries Are Transforming the World’s Electrical Grids Greek Police Say Eggs Were Stolen from IVF Clinic Patients ©2025 Bloomberg L.P. Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(18, 27, 'ORG'), (78, 95, 'DATE'), (120, 122, 'GPE'), (188, 193, 'GPE'), (220, 226, 'GPE'), (229, 242, 'MONEY'), (281, 290, 'ORG'), (291, 296, 'GPE'), (420, 425, 'PERSON'), (439, 441, 'GPE'), (465, 477, 'MONEY'), (483, 485, 'GPE'), (488, 494, 'PERSON'), (543, 545, 'GPE'), (679, 693, 'PERSON'), (720, 736, 'PERSON'), (740, 755, 'ORG'), (763, 787, 'EVENT'), (791, 796, 'GPE'), (800, 809, 'DATE'), (830, 835, 'DATE'), (917, 919, 'GPE'), (937, 942, 'GPE'), (1271, 1304, 'ORG'), (1345, 1359, 'DATE'), (1365, 1376, 'ORG'), (1407, 1411, 'DATE'), (1432, 1438, 'PERSON'), (1551, 1567, 'DATE'), (1575, 1581, 'PERSON'), (1694, 1696, 'GPE'), (1726, 1731, 'GPE'), (1733, 1737, 'ORG'), (1781, 1785, 'DATE'), (1789, 1796, 'DATE'), (1800, 1806, 'ORDINAL'), (1835, 1847, 'PERSON'), (1931, 1938, 'GPE'), (1998, 2004, 'LOC'), (2126, 2132, 'ORG'), (2545, 2547, 'GPE'), (2673, 2693, 'TIME'), (2828, 2832, 'DATE'), (2859, 2864, 'GPE'), (3049, 3061, 'CARDINAL'), (3104, 3113, 'DATE'), (3124, 3130, 'GPE'), (3240, 3256, 'ORG'), (3263, 3269, 'ORG'), (3283, 3287, 'ORG'), (3424, 3430, 'DATE'), (3576, 3578, 'GPE'), (3580, 3586, 'PERSON'), (3595, 3604, 'DATE'), (3645, 3649, 'ORG'), (3751, 3757, 'PERSON'), (3759, 3761, 'DATE'), (3899, 3908, 'NORP'), (3917, 3929, 'GPE'), (3963, 3972, 'NORP'), (4000, 4007, 'LANGUAGE'), (4071, 4085, 'ORG'), (4111, 4117, 'GPE'), (4143, 4158, 'ORG'), (4201, 4207, 'PERSON'), (4280, 4289, 'DATE'), (4303, 4309, 'PERSON'), (4569, 4578, 'DATE'), (4634, 4643, 'DATE'), (4661, 4670, 'DATE'), (4991, 5008, 'LAW'), (5221, 5254, 'ORG'), (5259, 5273, 'PERSON'), (5282, 5335, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (5340, 5360, 'ORG'), (5364, 5382, 'DATE'), (5386, 5395, 'TIME'), (5399, 5407, 'GPE'), (5412, 5420, 'DATE'), (5422, 5429, 'DATE'), (5433, 5442, 'TIME'), (5446, 5452, 'GPE'), (5477, 5496, 'PERSON'), (5501, 5516, 'PERSON'), (5564, 5570, 'ORDINAL'), (5598, 5620, 'ORG'), (5625, 5639, 'PERSON'), (5657, 5662, 'PERSON'), (5687, 5696, 'ORG'), (5750, 5762, 'MONEY'), (5770, 5781, 'PERSON'), (5871, 5876, 'NORP'), (5910, 5920, 'ORG'), (5936, 5950, 'ORG')]}"
"In This Article: LONDON (Reuters) - Shareholders in Herald Investment Trust on Wednesday rejected a campaign by U.S. activist investor Saba Capital to overhaul its board, in a blow to founder Boaz Weinstein's wider push to shake-up the UK's 269 billion pound ($333 billion) trust sector. ($1 = 0.8087 pounds) (Reporting by Iain Withers, editing by Sinead Cruise) Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(17, 23, 'GPE'), (25, 32, 'ORG'), (52, 75, 'ORG'), (79, 88, 'DATE'), (112, 116, 'GPE'), (135, 147, 'ORG'), (192, 206, 'PERSON'), (236, 238, 'GPE'), (241, 258, 'MONEY'), (260, 272, 'MONEY'), (290, 291, 'MONEY'), (294, 307, 'MONEY'), (323, 335, 'PERSON'), (348, 361, 'PERSON')]}"
"In This Article: JPMorgan Chase (JPM) CEO Jamie Dimon on Wednesday downplayed concerns about new tariffs from the Trump administration. ""People argue is it inflationary and not inflationary. I would put it in perspective, if it's a little inflationary, but it's good for national security, so be it. I mean, get over it,"" Dimon said while speaking with CNBC at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland. Tariffs ""are an economic tool. That's it. They're an economic weapon, depending how you use it, and why [you] use it,"" he added. Not that Dimon has completely dropped his long-running worries about other inflationary forces that could affect the US economy. ""I do have a little more caution around a bunch of subjects,"" Dimon said Wednesday. ""What I’m a little cautious about is the deficit spending; it’s a global issue, not just an American issue,"" he said. ""And the related [question], ‘Will inflation go away?’ I’m not so sure."" Dimon attracted a lot of attention at Davos last year when he said Trump was ""kind of right"" on some issues. Leading up to the US election, Dimon, who has been an outspoken voice on a range of issues, did not give a full-throated endorsement of either Vice President Kamala Harris or Trump, but he did offer them advice via informal and formal advisers to both candidates. After the election he said that people in his industry were ""dancing in the street"" as they anticipated more favorable treatment from a Republican administration. Dimon said Wednesday he hopes ""pro-growth strategies"" could help balance out some concerns he has about certain elements of the economy. ""Asset prices are kind of inflated"" in the stock market, he said. ""You need fairly good outcomes to justify those prices, and we’re all hoping for that. I think having pro-growth strategies helps make that happen, but there are negatives out there and they can tend to surprise you."" Dimon also discussed billionaire Elon Musk and the role he is playing in the new administration, as he leads a cost-cutting effort known as the Department of Government Efficiency. Dimon said he and Musk have ""settled some of our differences"" and he wishes Musk the best in the new effort. The two men had feuded for a number of years beginning in 2016 after JPMorgan refused to underwrite leases for Musk’s electric-vehicle maker, Tesla (TSLA). ""I think it is completely rational for someone to look at our government and say it’s been ineffective,"" Dimon said. ""Government needs to be more accountable, it needs to be more efficient, it should be outcomes-based."" Last week JPMorgan posted annual 2024 profits that amounted to its best year on record. It also announced a management shuffle that raised questions over who will be Dimon's ultimate replacement when he eventually decides to leave the bank. He told analysts a week ago that the base case for him stepping away as CEO is a few years from now. David Hollerith is a senior reporter for Yahoo Finance covering banking, crypto, and other areas in finance. Read the latest news and interviews from the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland: Trump should create a strategic bitcoin reserve: Coinbase CEO A trade war with China is coming as Trump takes office: Bremmer Bank of America CEO: The Federal Reserve may have to respond to Trump Suntory CEO says the company has stockpiled whiskey in Europe due to possible Trump tariffs Trump coin and Melania coin are 'gambling tokens': Anthony Scaramucci Federal Reserve could hike rates if Trump tariffs unleash inflation: BNY CEO Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(17, 31, 'ORG'), (33, 36, 'ORG'), (42, 53, 'PERSON'), (57, 66, 'DATE'), (322, 327, 'PERSON'), (353, 357, 'ORG'), (361, 385, 'ORG'), (389, 394, 'GPE'), (396, 407, 'GPE'), (547, 552, 'PERSON'), (655, 657, 'GPE'), (729, 734, 'PERSON'), (740, 749, 'DATE'), (843, 851, 'NORP'), (942, 947, 'PERSON'), (980, 985, 'GPE'), (986, 995, 'DATE'), (1009, 1014, 'PERSON'), (1069, 1071, 'GPE'), (1082, 1087, 'PERSON'), (1209, 1222, 'PERSON'), (1226, 1231, 'PERSON'), (1451, 1461, 'NORP'), (1478, 1483, 'PERSON'), (1489, 1498, 'DATE'), (1899, 1904, 'PERSON'), (1932, 1941, 'PERSON'), (2039, 2078, 'ORG'), (2080, 2085, 'PERSON'), (2098, 2102, 'PERSON'), (2156, 2160, 'PERSON'), (2193, 2196, 'CARDINAL'), (2228, 2233, 'DATE'), (2247, 2251, 'DATE'), (2258, 2266, 'ORG'), (2300, 2304, 'PERSON'), (2331, 2336, 'ORG'), (2338, 2342, 'ORG'), (2450, 2455, 'PERSON'), (2565, 2574, 'DATE'), (2575, 2583, 'ORG'), (2591, 2597, 'DATE'), (2598, 2602, 'DATE'), (2628, 2641, 'DATE'), (2731, 2736, 'PERSON'), (2823, 2833, 'DATE'), (2885, 2905, 'DATE'), (2907, 2922, 'PERSON'), (2948, 2961, 'ORG'), (3057, 3081, 'EVENT'), (3085, 3090, 'GPE'), (3092, 3103, 'GPE'), (3105, 3110, 'PERSON'), (3154, 3162, 'ORG'), (3184, 3189, 'GPE'), (3203, 3208, 'PERSON'), (3223, 3246, 'ORG'), (3252, 3271, 'ORG'), (3295, 3300, 'PERSON'), (3301, 3308, 'ORG'), (3356, 3362, 'LOC'), (3379, 3384, 'PERSON'), (3393, 3398, 'PERSON'), (3408, 3415, 'PERSON'), (3444, 3462, 'PERSON'), (3463, 3478, 'ORG'), (3499, 3504, 'PERSON'), (3532, 3535, 'ORG')]}"
"In This Article: The Federal Reserve now needs to be on Trump watch if it wants to engineer the proper dose of monetary policy, according to Bank of America chief Brian Moynihan. ""They've got a new administration with a new set of fiscal policies, and the monetary policy has to respond to that,"" the BofA chair and CEO told Yahoo Finance at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland. Moynihan added: ""We are not a central bank-led economy. We're actually a private sector-led economy, of which the government supports, of which the central bank responds to, and they have to think of what stimulus they're going to respond to."" The Fed, of course, is always one to play up its independence from the White House. What has unnerved the markets to start 2025 is the Federal Reserve not committing to aggressive rate cutting, alongside a stronger-than-expected US economy. The consensus among Fed officials is now for two rate cuts this year, down from the four forecast in September. The monetary policy body remains concerned about inflation — San Francisco Fed president Mary Daly was non-committal on more rate cuts on Yahoo Finance's Opening Bid podcast recently. Read more: What the Fed rate cut means for bank accounts, CDs, loans, and credit cards Potential moves by the Trump administration, such as tariffs on China, further cloud the outlook for inflation. Not helping matters is the renewed rise in oil prices to kick off the year. The US economy has also shown impressive resilience, including a blowout December jobs report. ""The fact that the narrative has shifted is because the economy is stronger because the labor market is stronger,"" BlackRock's chief investment and portfolio strategist for the Americas, Gargi Chaudhuri, said on Opening Bid. ""I think one to two more rate cuts in this cycle based on the data at hand, is fair to assume with a very open mindset."" Despite the Fed uncertainty, Bank of America shares have rallied 11.5% since Donald Trump's election win in November. The S&P 500 is up 4.7% during that same stretch. Bank industry experts say the rally reflects potential lighter regulations under Trump, particularly on the capital requirements front. ""I think what we want to see is capital [requirements] a little more rational,"" Moynihan said on what he'd like to see from the Trump administration. ""And then secondly, you want to take a look at some liquidity and other rules, which got stacked up and actually have an adverse effect on carrying capital, which doesn't make a lot of sense because some of the other tedious things that go on banking regulation."" ""And then you want to look at regulation around consumer activities and keep it balanced,"" he added. The banking sector has had a bang-up fourth quarter, and CEOs at the major firms voiced optimism on sales and profits outlooks. Fourth quarter results for Goldman Sachs (GS), JP Morgan (JPM), and Citi (C) were powered by bumper sales in investment banking and trading businesses. Bank of America participated in the Wall Street revival to cap off 2024. The company's revenue increased 15%, with net earnings up 111%. Total investment banking fees rose 44%. Global markets sales improved by 18%. ""Credit quality remains strong underlying the conservative approach to underwriting, in our view. Additionally, the company is well capitalized and should continue to return capital of shareholders in the form of dividends and stock buybacks,"" RBC Capital Markets analyst Gerard Cassidy said following Bank of America's Q4 earnings results. — Brian Sozzi is Yahoo Finance's Executive Editor. Follow Sozzi on X @BrianSozzi, Instagram, and on LinkedIn. Tips on stories? Email brian.sozzi@yahoofinance.com. Three times each week, Sozzi fields insight-filled conversations with the biggest names in business and markets on Yahoo Finance's Opening Bid podcast. Find more episodes on our video hub. Watch on your preferred streaming service. Or listen and subscribe on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you find your favorite podcasts. Read the latest news and interviews from the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland: A trade war with China is coming as Trump takes office: Bremmer Trump coin and Melania coin are 'gambling tokens': Anthony Scaramucci Trump, tariffs, crypto, and everything else that will dominate Davos Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(17, 36, 'ORG'), (56, 61, 'PERSON'), (141, 156, 'ORG'), (163, 177, 'PERSON'), (301, 305, 'ORG'), (325, 338, 'ORG'), (342, 366, 'EVENT'), (370, 375, 'GPE'), (377, 388, 'GPE'), (390, 398, 'PERSON'), (638, 641, 'ORG'), (701, 716, 'ORG'), (757, 761, 'DATE'), (765, 784, 'ORG'), (863, 865, 'GPE'), (895, 898, 'ORG'), (920, 923, 'CARDINAL'), (934, 943, 'DATE'), (959, 963, 'CARDINAL'), (976, 985, 'DATE'), (1048, 1065, 'ORG'), (1076, 1085, 'PERSON'), (1125, 1140, 'ORG'), (1141, 1152, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (1191, 1194, 'ORG'), (1281, 1286, 'PERSON'), (1322, 1327, 'GPE'), (1436, 1444, 'DATE'), (1450, 1452, 'GPE'), (1519, 1527, 'DATE'), (1656, 1665, 'ORG'), (1718, 1726, 'LOC'), (1728, 1743, 'PERSON'), (1753, 1764, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (1775, 1778, 'CARDINAL'), (1899, 1902, 'ORG'), (1916, 1931, 'ORG'), (1952, 1957, 'PERCENT'), (1964, 1978, 'PERSON'), (1995, 2003, 'DATE'), (2023, 2027, 'PERCENT'), (2135, 2140, 'PERSON'), (2270, 2278, 'PERSON'), (2318, 2323, 'PERSON'), (2350, 2358, 'ORDINAL'), (2732, 2756, 'DATE'), (2833, 2847, 'DATE'), (2860, 2873, 'ORG'), (2875, 2877, 'ORG'), (2880, 2889, 'ORG'), (2891, 2894, 'ORG'), (2901, 2905, 'ORG'), (2907, 2908, 'ORG'), (2985, 3000, 'ORG'), (3052, 3056, 'DATE'), (3090, 3093, 'PERCENT'), (3116, 3120, 'PERCENT'), (3157, 3160, 'PERCENT'), (3195, 3198, 'PERCENT'), (3444, 3463, 'ORG'), (3472, 3486, 'PERSON'), (3502, 3519, 'ORG'), (3520, 3522, 'DATE'), (3543, 3554, 'PERSON'), (3558, 3573, 'ORG'), (3599, 3604, 'PERSON'), (3623, 3632, 'ORG'), (3641, 3649, 'ORG'), (3704, 3709, 'CARDINAL'), (3716, 3725, 'DATE'), (3727, 3732, 'PERSON'), (3819, 3834, 'ORG'), (3835, 3846, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (3963, 3977, 'ORG'), (3979, 3986, 'ORG'), (4074, 4098, 'ORG'), (4102, 4107, 'GPE'), (4109, 4120, 'GPE'), (4139, 4144, 'GPE'), (4158, 4163, 'PERSON'), (4186, 4191, 'PERSON'), (4201, 4208, 'PERSON'), (4237, 4261, 'PERSON'), (4319, 4324, 'GPE')]}"
"P&G Stopped Hiking Prices and Sales Still Grew Last Quarter In This Article: (Bloomberg) -- Procter & Gamble Co. organic sales surpassed estimates on higher volume, a change from earlier quarters where most of the company’s growth came from price hikes. Most Read from Bloomberg Texas HOA Charged With Discrimination for Banning Section 8 Renters How Sanctuary Cities Are Preparing for Another Showdown With Trump Donations to LA Fire Victims Rise Past $200 Million Mark NY’s Hochul Calls for Law Banning Cell Phone Use in Schools LA Schools Wrecked by Fires Plead on GoFundMe for Help to Reopen Organic sales rose 3% in the three months ended Dec. 31, P&G said Wednesday, the biggest increase in three quarters. Most of that was due to higher volume, meaning retailers bought more essentials like Dawn dish soap and Gillette razors to restock their shelves. Prices were unchanged compared with the year-earlier quarter, the first time they haven’t risen since 2019. The shares rose as much as 4% as of 9:40 a.m. in New York, their biggest intraday gain in about a year. The results suggest that the era of endless price hikes may be waning. Companies that make consumer package goods have for years counted on price increases to help fuel revenue growth. In P&G’s fiscal year that ended last June, prices were 4% higher compared to the year earlier, when they jumped 9%. “We believe P&G remains one of the best-positioned CPG companies to deal with the volatility that has come to define the past few years and most likely the next few years,” RBC Capital Markets analyst Nik Modi said in a research note Wednesday. Companies are under pressure to slow inflation as President Donald Trump takes office. In an executive order issued Jan. 20, Trump said consumers are facing a “cost-of-living crisis” and that it’s “critical to restore purchasing power to the American family.” “We see consumers trading up,” Andre Schulten, P&G’s chief financial officer, said in an interview. “They’re trading into either bigger pack sizes or they’re trading into higher-value items.” Schulten said P&G is responding to the cost-of-living crisis reflected in Trump’s executive order by innovating on less-expensive items, such as Luvs baby diapers, which were relaunched with an upgraded diaper last year. “We recognized the consumer was looking for more innovation on the value tier,” he said. “The consumer is responding. We are growing share.” P&G said innovation helped drive growth in its grooming and oral-care businesses. The company has been creating new products that it can charge more for, including all-over body deodorant and razors for different body parts. P&G has also been trying to get its products on more end caps in retail stores to encourage more impromptu purchases. Sales were also bolstered by P&G’s fabric and home care segment — the company’s largest business which includes the Tide and Swiffer brands — and double-digit gains in the segment that makes Bounty paper towels and Charmin toilet paper. P&G said some consumers stocked up on paper products in October during the port strike and hurricane. Meanwhile, the beauty division was hurt by volume declines in Greater China, where P&G has said lower consumer confidence is weakening the business. Schulten said organic sales in China were down 3% for the quarter. P&G believes it will take some time before the China business returns to consistent growth. The company reiterated its guidance for sales and profit in the current fiscal year, which goes through the end of June. P&G is among the first consumer companies to report earnings in the US. It gets roughly half of its revenue from North America. Like other consumer-staples companies, shares of P&G have underperformed the broader market over the past year. The stock had gained less than 10% in the 12 months ended Jan. 21, compared with a 25% increase in the S&P 500. (Updates with shares in third paragraph, analyst comment in fifth.) Most Read from Bloomberg Businessweek How Kendrick Lamar Turned Beef With Drake Into Music Superstardom Walgreens Replaced Fridge Doors With Smart Screens. It’s Now a $200 Million Fiasco Elon Musk’s Inaugural Highs (and Lows) Giant Batteries Are Transforming the World’s Electrical Grids Greek Police Say Eggs Were Stolen from IVF Clinic Patients ©2025 Bloomberg L.P. Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(0, 3, 'ORG'), (47, 59, 'DATE'), (78, 87, 'ORG'), (92, 112, 'ORG'), (179, 195, 'DATE'), (269, 278, 'ORG'), (279, 284, 'GPE'), (408, 413, 'PERSON'), (427, 429, 'GPE'), (453, 465, 'MONEY'), (471, 473, 'GPE'), (531, 533, 'GPE'), (615, 617, 'PERCENT'), (621, 651, 'DATE'), (653, 656, 'ORG'), (662, 671, 'DATE'), (697, 711, 'DATE'), (798, 802, 'PRODUCT'), (817, 825, 'ORG'), (895, 919, 'DATE'), (925, 930, 'ORDINAL'), (961, 965, 'DATE'), (983, 996, 'PERCENT'), (1003, 1012, 'TIME'), (1016, 1024, 'GPE'), (1040, 1048, 'TIME'), (1057, 1069, 'DATE'), (1194, 1199, 'DATE'), (1259, 1262, 'ORG'), (1265, 1276, 'DATE'), (1288, 1297, 'DATE'), (1311, 1313, 'PERCENT'), (1333, 1349, 'DATE'), (1368, 1370, 'PERCENT'), (1384, 1387, 'ORG'), (1423, 1426, 'ORG'), (1489, 1507, 'DATE'), (1524, 1542, 'DATE'), (1545, 1564, 'ORG'), (1573, 1581, 'PERSON'), (1606, 1615, 'DATE'), (1677, 1689, 'PERSON'), (1733, 1740, 'DATE'), (1742, 1747, 'PERSON'), (1859, 1867, 'NORP'), (1908, 1922, 'PERSON'), (1924, 1927, 'ORG'), (2069, 2077, 'PERSON'), (2083, 2086, 'ORG'), (2143, 2148, 'PERSON'), (2214, 2218, 'ORG'), (2279, 2288, 'DATE'), (2431, 2434, 'ORG'), (2656, 2659, 'ORG'), (2803, 2806, 'ORG'), (2890, 2894, 'ORG'), (2899, 2906, 'PRODUCT'), (2965, 2971, 'ORG'), (2989, 2996, 'PRODUCT'), (3011, 3014, 'ORG'), (3067, 3074, 'DATE'), (3183, 3188, 'GPE'), (3196, 3199, 'ORG'), (3262, 3270, 'ORG'), (3293, 3298, 'GPE'), (3309, 3311, 'PERCENT'), (3316, 3327, 'DATE'), (3329, 3332, 'ORG'), (3376, 3381, 'GPE'), (3481, 3504, 'DATE'), (3525, 3540, 'DATE'), (3542, 3545, 'ORG'), (3559, 3564, 'ORDINAL'), (3610, 3612, 'GPE'), (3622, 3634, 'CARDINAL'), (3655, 3668, 'LOC'), (3719, 3722, 'ORG'), (3767, 3780, 'DATE'), (3803, 3816, 'PERCENT'), (3820, 3847, 'DATE'), (3865, 3868, 'PERCENT'), (3918, 3923, 'ORDINAL'), (3954, 3959, 'ORDINAL'), (3977, 3999, 'ORG'), (4004, 4018, 'PERSON'), (4036, 4041, 'PERSON'), (4066, 4075, 'ORG'), (4129, 4141, 'MONEY'), (4149, 4160, 'PERSON'), (4250, 4255, 'NORP'), (4289, 4299, 'ORG'), (4315, 4329, 'ORG')]}"
"In This Article: The artificial intelligence sector remains a hot investing theme this year. Enterprises and cloud-service providers are ramping up their investments in data center infrastructure to support growing demand. 💸Limited time! Get TheStreet Pro’s quarterly call for free. Expert analysts and fund managers share their 2025 strategies. Start your free trial today.💸 ""AI-related [semiconductor] stocks led the [PHLX SemiconductorSector] in '23 and '24. We see '25 as more of the same as [chip scale package capital spending] continues to rise and enterprises work to monetize their AI strategies,"" said Oppenheimer analyst Rick Schafer. GPUs and custom chips designed for AI workloads have generated significant growth under such demand, with Nvidia  (NVDA)  standing out as a leading force in the industry. Schafer has named Nvidia and three other stocks as Oppenheimer's top stock picks for 2025. Nvidia maintains its dominance Nvidia is ""the largest volume producer of AI accelerators and the cost-per-bit leader in AI training,"" Schafer said. The company’s dominance comes from its full-stack approach to AI infrastructure, which includes a comprehensive portfolio of hardware and software ranging from AI graphics-processing units to networking components such as switches, NICs, InfiniBand, and NVLink, as well as its CUDA software platform. Related: Tech heavyweight launches AI chips that can compete with Nvidia A key driver of Nvidia’s growth in 2025 is its next-generation Blackwell architecture. ""Demand continues to outpace supply,"" Schafer noted. Oppenheimer estimates that Nvidia's data center AI-related sales in 2025 will reach $172 billion. Meanwhile, Nvidia's competitors struggle to keep up. Oppenheimer anticipates AMD’s  (AMD)  AI sales at $7.5 billion for the year, falling short of buyside estimates of $9 billion to $10 billion. Nvidia stock advanced more than 170% in 2024, making it one of the top performers in the Dow and the S&P 500. Yet Oppenheimer said the stock was trading at a valuation below its historical multiples, which likely means a discounted trading price and further room for growth. ""Nvidia trades at 25 times our [calendar year 2026 estimated earnings per share] versus three- and five-year averages of 34 times and 37 times,"" Schafer added. The investment firm has an outperform rating for Nvidia with a price target of $175. The stock closed 2.3% higher at $140.83 on Jan. 21. The target indicates potential upside of 24%. Three other top picks: Monolithic, Broadcom, Marvell Schafer also included Broadcom, Marvell and Monolithic Power Systems in the top-stock-pick list. Monolithic Power Systems  (MPWR)  supplies 48V power systems to major AI players like Nvidia, AMD, Amazon, and Google. Oppenheimer sees long-term growth as the market shifts to higher-power modules. However, major client Nvidia’s decision to reduce purchases from Monolithic for its Blackwell platform could bring short-term pressure to the power-tech provider. Sales to Nvidia are expected to fall by half this year to $200 million, the investment firm said. Monolithic Power Systems shares eased 6.2% in 2024. They've tumbled 30% in the past three months even after the company posted strong Q3 earnings in October. Monolithic closed at $638.49, up 2%, on Jan. 21. Oppenheimer has an outperform rating and a price target of $900 on the shares. Broadcom and Marvell continue to shine in 2025 Broadcom and Marvell saw major gains in 2024, with shares surging 107.7% and 83.1%, respectively, driven by their strong roles in AI and data center markets. Broadcom  (AVGO)  designs custom chips for tech giants like Google, Meta, ByteDance, OpenAI and Apple. In 2024, Broadcom's AI revenue exceeded $12 billion, tripling year-over-year. Related: Top analyst revisits Broadcom stock price target amid December surge ""AVGO benefits as [cloud-service providers] scale AI clusters from hundreds of thousands to over 1 million connected [X processing units],"" Schafer wrote. He also highlighted the company's profitability, ""with 77% gross margin, 60% operating margin, and 38% free cash flow margin."" Marvell  (MRVL)  is the second-largest custom application-specific integrated circuit, or ASIC, provider, with key partners including Amazon, Google and Microsoft. The company's data center sales in the recently reported October quarter nearly doubled year-over-year and moved up 25% sequentially, reaching $1.1 billion. The company’s AI-related sales are expected to exceed $1.5 billion in the current fiscal year and $2.5 billion in 2025, CEO Matt Murphy said during the earnings call. Oppenheimer has a yet more bullish estimate. More 2025 stock market forecasts Stocks face correction risk as Santa Claus Rally fails to deliver Veteran trader who correctly picked Palantir as top stock in ‘24 reveals best stock for ‘25 5 quantum computing stocks investors are targeting in 2025 Goldman Sachs picks top sectors to own in 2025 ""We estimate custom ASIC revenue could approach $4 billion this year, roughly double buyside expectations,"" Schafer said. Oppenheimer has an outperform rating on both Marvell and Broadcom, with target prices of $125 and $225, respectively. On Jan. 21 Marvell closed off 0.8% at $123.78. Broadcom shares tacked on 1,2% to $240.31. Oppenheimer's four stock picks for 2025 are the same selections the firm made for the previous year. Nvidia, Broadcom and Marvell were also big winners in 2024. Related: Veteran fund manager issues dire S&P 500 warning for 2025 Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(82, 91, 'DATE'), (224, 236, 'TIME'), (242, 257, 'ORG'), (258, 267, 'DATE'), (329, 333, 'DATE'), (368, 373, 'DATE'), (449, 452, 'DATE'), (457, 460, 'DATE'), (469, 472, 'DATE'), (612, 623, 'ORG'), (632, 644, 'PERSON'), (752, 758, 'ORG'), (761, 765, 'ORG'), (817, 824, 'PERSON'), (835, 841, 'ORG'), (846, 851, 'CARDINAL'), (868, 879, 'ORG'), (902, 906, 'DATE'), (908, 914, 'ORG'), (939, 945, 'ORG'), (1042, 1049, 'PERSON'), (1294, 1304, 'PRODUCT'), (1310, 1316, 'PRODUCT'), (1333, 1337, 'PRODUCT'), (1423, 1429, 'ORG'), (1446, 1452, 'ORG'), (1465, 1469, 'DATE'), (1493, 1502, 'PRODUCT'), (1555, 1562, 'PERSON'), (1570, 1581, 'ORG'), (1597, 1603, 'ORG'), (1638, 1642, 'DATE'), (1654, 1666, 'MONEY'), (1679, 1685, 'ORG'), (1721, 1732, 'ORG'), (1745, 1748, 'ORG'), (1753, 1756, 'ORG'), (1771, 1783, 'MONEY'), (1788, 1796, 'DATE'), (1836, 1861, 'MONEY'), (1863, 1869, 'ORG'), (1885, 1899, 'PERCENT'), (1903, 1907, 'DATE'), (1952, 1955, 'ORG'), (1977, 1988, 'ORG'), (2139, 2145, 'ORG'), (2156, 2158, 'CARDINAL'), (2170, 2188, 'DATE'), (2237, 2246, 'DATE'), (2259, 2261, 'CARDINAL'), (2272, 2274, 'CARDINAL'), (2283, 2290, 'PERSON'), (2347, 2353, 'ORG'), (2378, 2381, 'MONEY'), (2400, 2404, 'PERCENT'), (2416, 2422, 'MONEY'), (2426, 2433, 'DATE'), (2476, 2479, 'PERCENT'), (2481, 2486, 'CARDINAL'), (2504, 2514, 'ORG'), (2516, 2524, 'ORG'), (2526, 2541, 'ORG'), (2556, 2564, 'ORG'), (2566, 2574, 'ORG'), (2578, 2602, 'ORG'), (2631, 2655, 'ORG'), (2658, 2662, 'ORG'), (2717, 2723, 'ORG'), (2725, 2728, 'ORG'), (2730, 2736, 'ORG'), (2742, 2748, 'ORG'), (2750, 2761, 'ORG'), (2852, 2858, 'ORG'), (2895, 2905, 'ORG'), (2914, 2923, 'PRODUCT'), (3002, 3008, 'ORG'), (3033, 3037, 'CARDINAL'), (3038, 3047, 'DATE'), (3051, 3063, 'MONEY'), (3091, 3115, 'ORG'), (3129, 3133, 'PERCENT'), (3137, 3141, 'DATE'), (3159, 3162, 'PERCENT'), (3166, 3187, 'DATE'), (3225, 3227, 'DATE'), (3240, 3247, 'DATE'), (3249, 3259, 'ORG'), (3271, 3277, 'MONEY'), (3282, 3284, 'PERCENT'), (3289, 3296, 'DATE'), (3298, 3309, 'ORG'), (3358, 3361, 'MONEY'), (3377, 3385, 'ORG'), (3390, 3397, 'ORG'), (3419, 3423, 'DATE'), (3424, 3432, 'ORG'), (3437, 3444, 'ORG'), (3464, 3468, 'DATE'), (3490, 3496, 'PERCENT'), (3501, 3506, 'PERCENT'), (3582, 3590, 'ORG'), (3593, 3597, 'ORG'), (3642, 3648, 'ORG'), (3650, 3654, 'ORG'), (3656, 3665, 'ORG'), (3667, 3673, 'ORG'), (3678, 3683, 'ORG'), (3688, 3692, 'DATE'), (3694, 3702, 'ORG'), (3725, 3736, 'MONEY'), (3747, 3761, 'DATE'), (3793, 3801, 'ORG'), (3826, 3834, 'DATE'), (3842, 3846, 'ORG'), (3908, 3929, 'CARDINAL'), (3933, 3947, 'CARDINAL'), (3981, 3988, 'PERSON'), (4051, 4054, 'PERCENT'), (4069, 4072, 'PERCENT'), (4095, 4098, 'PERCENT'), (4123, 4130, 'ORG'), (4133, 4137, 'ORG'), (4147, 4153, 'ORDINAL'), (4257, 4263, 'ORG'), (4265, 4271, 'ORG'), (4276, 4285, 'ORG'), (4322, 4359, 'DATE'), (4385, 4389, 'DATE'), (4403, 4406, 'PERCENT'), (4430, 4442, 'MONEY'), (4498, 4510, 'MONEY'), (4514, 4537, 'DATE'), (4542, 4554, 'MONEY'), (4558, 4562, 'DATE'), (4568, 4579, 'PERSON'), (4611, 4622, 'ORG'), (4661, 4665, 'DATE'), (4720, 4737, 'EVENT'), (4791, 4799, 'ORG'), (4816, 4819, 'DATE'), (4843, 4846, 'DATE'), (4847, 4848, 'CARDINAL'), (4901, 4905, 'DATE'), (4906, 4919, 'ORG'), (4948, 4952, 'DATE'), (5001, 5011, 'MONEY'), (5012, 5021, 'DATE'), (5061, 5068, 'PERSON'), (5075, 5086, 'ORG'), (5120, 5127, 'ORG'), (5132, 5140, 'ORG'), (5165, 5168, 'MONEY'), (5174, 5177, 'MONEY'), (5196, 5203, 'DATE'), (5204, 5211, 'ORG'), (5223, 5227, 'PERCENT'), (5232, 5238, 'MONEY'), (5240, 5248, 'ORG'), (5266, 5270, 'PERCENT'), (5275, 5281, 'MONEY'), (5283, 5294, 'ORG'), (5297, 5301, 'CARDINAL'), (5318, 5322, 'DATE'), (5365, 5382, 'DATE'), (5384, 5390, 'ORG'), (5392, 5400, 'ORG'), (5405, 5412, 'ORG'), (5438, 5442, 'DATE'), (5506, 5510, 'DATE')]}"
"In This Article: Nvidia (NVDA) stock jumped more than 4% Wednesday, extending gains from the prior day following Trump’s announcement of a massive, $500 billion AI infrastructure project. The project creates a company called Stargate, funded by SoftBank (9984.T), OpenAI, Oracle (ORCL), and MGX. OpenAI named Nvidia as well as Microsoft (MSFT) and British chip designer Arm (ARM) as “key initial technology partners” for the project, which aims to build out US data centers required to power artificial intelligence. OpenAI said Stargate would “begin deploying $100 billion immediately"" and invest up to $500 billion over the next four years. Nvidia's gain Wednesday pushed its market cap to $3.58 trillion, ahead of Apple's (AAPL) $3.35 trillion. Meanwhile, Microsoft shares rose 3% early Wednesday, while Arm surged more than 15%. Oracle stock was up 5.5%, and Softbank jumped almost 11%. “Stargate will be building the physical and virtual infrastructure to power the next generation of advancements in AI, and this will include the construction of colossal data centers, very, very massive structures,” Trump said in a briefing Tuesday. “These buildings, these are big, beautiful buildings are going to employ a lot of people.” Trump said the effort is meant to maintain the US lead ahead in developing artificial intelligence ahead of China. The announcement follows a a slew of executive orders from the Biden administration on artificial intelligence last week aimed at restricting the flow of AI chips to China and speeding up the construction of data centers in the US. ""This comes at a critical juncture as we expect Trump to aggressively court more AI investments in the US,"" wrote Wedbush analyst Dan Ives in a note to investors late Tuesday. Ives noted that the project is ""all part of a broader game of high stakes poker with China."" After the announcement, Elon Musk took aim at OpenAI on his social media platform X. Responding to a post from OpenAI about Stargate, he wrote ""They don’t actually have the money."" OpenAI estimated that it lost $5 billion in 2024, but generated just $3.7 billion in revenue. Tech stocks across the board rallied on the news of the major AI investment. Dell (DELL) and Super Micro Computer (SMCI), which make servers using Nvidia chips, rose 7% and 6%, respectively. Nasdaq futures (NQ=F) climbed 1.4%, ahead of S&P Futures' (ES=F) 0.6% gain. Nvidia’s surge Wednesday puts shares up over 11% from last week. The stock had fallen in early January after The Information reported that the three of the chipmaker’s biggest customers — Amazon (AMZN), Google (GOOG), and Meta (META) — canceled some orders of servers using Nvidia Blackwell AI chips due to glitches and overheating problems. Shares were also under pressure from the Biden administration’s move to cap exports of AI chips. Laura Bratton is a reporter for Yahoo Finance. Follow her on Bluesky @laurabratton.bsky.social. Email her at laura.bratton@yahooinc.com. Click here for the latest stock market news and in-depth analysis, including events that move stocks Read the latest financial and business news from Yahoo Finance Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(17, 23, 'ORG'), (25, 29, 'ORG'), (44, 56, 'PERCENT'), (57, 66, 'DATE'), (89, 102, 'DATE'), (113, 118, 'PERSON'), (148, 160, 'MONEY'), (225, 233, 'ORG'), (245, 253, 'ORG'), (255, 261, 'ORG'), (264, 270, 'ORG'), (272, 278, 'ORG'), (280, 284, 'ORG'), (291, 294, 'ORG'), (296, 302, 'ORG'), (309, 315, 'ORG'), (327, 336, 'ORG'), (338, 342, 'ORG'), (348, 355, 'NORP'), (370, 373, 'ORG'), (375, 378, 'ORG'), (458, 460, 'GPE'), (517, 523, 'ORG'), (529, 537, 'ORG'), (561, 573, 'MONEY'), (598, 616, 'MONEY'), (622, 641, 'DATE'), (643, 649, 'ORG'), (657, 666, 'DATE'), (692, 706, 'MONEY'), (717, 722, 'ORG'), (726, 730, 'ORG'), (732, 746, 'MONEY'), (759, 768, 'ORG'), (781, 783, 'PERCENT'), (784, 799, 'DATE'), (807, 810, 'ORG'), (818, 831, 'PERCENT'), (833, 839, 'ORG'), (853, 857, 'PERCENT'), (863, 871, 'ORG'), (879, 889, 'PERCENT'), (892, 900, 'ORG'), (1107, 1112, 'PERSON'), (1132, 1139, 'DATE'), (1232, 1237, 'PERSON'), (1279, 1281, 'GPE'), (1340, 1345, 'GPE'), (1410, 1415, 'PERSON'), (1458, 1467, 'DATE'), (1513, 1518, 'GPE'), (1575, 1577, 'GPE'), (1627, 1632, 'PERSON'), (1682, 1684, 'GPE'), (1693, 1700, 'ORG'), (1709, 1717, 'PERSON'), (1741, 1753, 'DATE'), (1755, 1759, 'PERSON'), (1840, 1845, 'GPE'), (1872, 1881, 'PERSON'), (1894, 1900, 'ORG'), (1959, 1965, 'ORG'), (1972, 1980, 'PRODUCT'), (2029, 2035, 'ORG'), (2059, 2069, 'MONEY'), (2073, 2077, 'DATE'), (2093, 2110, 'MONEY'), (2200, 2204, 'ORG'), (2206, 2210, 'ORG'), (2216, 2236, 'ORG'), (2238, 2242, 'ORG'), (2270, 2276, 'ORG'), (2289, 2291, 'PERCENT'), (2296, 2298, 'PERCENT'), (2314, 2320, 'ORG'), (2344, 2348, 'PERCENT'), (2359, 2370, 'ORG'), (2379, 2383, 'PERCENT'), (2390, 2396, 'ORG'), (2405, 2414, 'DATE'), (2430, 2438, 'PERCENT'), (2444, 2453, 'DATE'), (2479, 2492, 'DATE'), (2503, 2514, 'ORG'), (2533, 2538, 'CARDINAL'), (2578, 2584, 'ORG'), (2586, 2590, 'ORG'), (2593, 2599, 'ORG'), (2601, 2605, 'ORG'), (2612, 2616, 'ORG'), (2618, 2622, 'ORG'), (2664, 2670, 'ORG'), (2671, 2680, 'PRODUCT'), (2773, 2778, 'PERSON'), (2829, 2842, 'PERSON'), (2861, 2874, 'ORG'), (2890, 2897, 'ORG'), (3116, 3129, 'ORG')]}"
"(Bloomberg) -- Venture Global Inc. slashed the marketed range for its initial public offering, bringing the potential valuation well below its $110 billion target. Most Read from Bloomberg Texas HOA Charged With Discrimination for Banning Section 8 Renters How Sanctuary Cities Are Preparing for Another Showdown With Trump Donations to LA Fire Victims Rise Past $200 Million Mark NY’s Hochul Calls for Law Banning Cell Phone Use in Schools LA Schools Wrecked by Fires Plead on GoFundMe for Help to Reopen The liquefied natural gas exporter is marketing 70 million shares in the offering for $23 to $27 each, a more than 40% drop from the $40 to $46 per share range it had targeted earlier, according to an earlier filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission. At the top of the new range, the company would raise $1.9 billion in the listing, and would have a market value of about $65 billion, based on the outstanding shares. Investors approached during the marketing of the deal wanted a lower valuation range, according to people familiar with the matter, who asked not to be identified as the information isn’t public. A representative for Venture Global didn’t immediately respond to requests for comment. The lower pricing would come as a setback for potential IPO candidates in the US energy sector, which have been looking to Venture Global’s offering to help revive sentiment around first-time share sales in the sector. Just six energy IPOs priced on US exchanges in 2024, raising $667 million to mark the lowest volume for energy IPOs in 21 years, data compiled by Bloomberg show. Still, Venture Global is targeting a lofty valuation relative to competitors. Cheniere Energy Inc., the largest LNG exporter in the US, has a market value of $54 billion after jumping 48% over the past year. Venture Global, founded outside of Washington, DC, was viewed as a startup compared to the established energy companies and climbed to quickly build two export facilities in Louisiana. The company is locked in arbitration battles with some of the world’s biggest energy players, which are also its customers. BP Plc and Shell Plc are in a dispute with Venture Global over its first plant, Calcasieu Pass, due to a prolonged start to their contracts almost three years since the facility first began loading cargoes. Venture Global had net income of $756 million in the nine months ended Sept. 30 on revenue of $3.4 billion, versus net income of $3.6 billion on revenue of $6.3 billion in the same period in 2023, according to the filing. LNG is expected to play an increasingly central role in global energy markets in the years ahead, as nations seek a cleaner-burning alternative to oil and coal. The US’s position as the world’s largest supplier of the fuel is poised to grow even stronger, as Donald Trump’s return to the White House was accompanied by a sweeping overhaul of US energy policy to return the emphasis to fossil-fuel production. --With assistance from Bre Bradham. (Updates prospective offer size in third paragraph and Cheniere market value in sixth paragraph.) Most Read from Bloomberg Businessweek How Kendrick Lamar Turned Beef With Drake Into Music Superstardom Walgreens Replaced Fridge Doors With Smart Screens. It’s Now a $200 Million Fiasco Elon Musk’s Inaugural Highs (and Lows) Giant Batteries Are Transforming the World’s Electrical Grids Greek Police Say Eggs Were Stolen from IVF Clinic Patients ©2025 Bloomberg L.P. Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(1, 10, 'ORG'), (15, 34, 'ORG'), (143, 155, 'MONEY'), (179, 188, 'ORG'), (189, 194, 'GPE'), (247, 248, 'CARDINAL'), (318, 323, 'PERSON'), (337, 339, 'GPE'), (363, 375, 'MONEY'), (381, 383, 'GPE'), (386, 392, 'PERSON'), (441, 443, 'GPE'), (554, 564, 'CARDINAL'), (592, 602, 'MONEY'), (611, 624, 'PERCENT'), (639, 649, 'MONEY'), (727, 768, 'ORG'), (823, 835, 'MONEY'), (885, 902, 'MONEY'), (1154, 1168, 'ORG'), (1299, 1301, 'GPE'), (1344, 1360, 'ORG'), (1402, 1407, 'ORDINAL'), (1440, 1448, 'CARDINAL'), (1471, 1473, 'GPE'), (1501, 1513, 'MONEY'), (1559, 1567, 'DATE'), (1586, 1595, 'ORG'), (1609, 1623, 'ORG'), (1680, 1700, 'ORG'), (1734, 1736, 'GPE'), (1760, 1771, 'MONEY'), (1786, 1789, 'PERCENT'), (1795, 1808, 'DATE'), (1810, 1824, 'ORG'), (1845, 1859, 'GPE'), (1959, 1962, 'CARDINAL'), (1984, 1993, 'GPE'), (2119, 2125, 'ORG'), (2130, 2139, 'ORG'), (2162, 2176, 'ORG'), (2186, 2191, 'ORDINAL'), (2199, 2213, 'FAC'), (2259, 2277, 'DATE'), (2326, 2340, 'ORG'), (2359, 2371, 'MONEY'), (2375, 2405, 'DATE'), (2420, 2432, 'MONEY'), (2455, 2467, 'MONEY'), (2482, 2494, 'MONEY'), (2517, 2521, 'DATE'), (2629, 2644, 'DATE'), (2713, 2715, 'GPE'), (2807, 2821, 'PERSON'), (2832, 2847, 'ORG'), (2890, 2892, 'GPE'), (2980, 2991, 'PERSON'), (3028, 3033, 'ORDINAL'), (3048, 3056, 'ORG'), (3073, 3078, 'ORDINAL'), (3106, 3128, 'ORG'), (3133, 3147, 'PERSON'), (3165, 3170, 'PERSON'), (3195, 3204, 'ORG'), (3258, 3270, 'MONEY'), (3278, 3289, 'PERSON'), (3379, 3384, 'NORP'), (3444, 3458, 'ORG')]}"
"A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan Retaining a persistent, if uncertain, threat of new tariffs, U.S. President Donald Trump quickly switched his attention to technology and artificial intelligence this week - exciting the red-hot sector that's about to report its latest earnings round. Trump on Tuesday announced a private sector investment of up to $500 billion to fund infrastructure for artificial intelligence, aiming to outpace rival nations in the business-critical technology. The newly sworn-in President said ChatGPT creator OpenAI, SoftBank and Oracle plan a joint venture called Stargate, which he said will build data centers and create more than 100,000 jobs in the United States. Softbank shares soared more than 10% in Tokyo trading, while Oracle surged 9% out of hours ahead of Wednesday's bell. With the fizz back in tech, streaming giant Netflix burst 14% higher in premarket trade on Wednesday after its latest earnings update revealed a record 18.9 million new subscribers over the holiday quarter and plans for price hikes. The renewed tech focus comes as the Nasdaq has marginally underperformed the broader S&P500 so far this year, with even Apple under a cloud on Tuesday despite brisk Wall Street stock index gains. The Apple retreat allowed AI-chip darling Nvidia to retake top spot as America's most valuable company. With some big industrial names topping the corporate diary on Wednesday, and the first 10% of S&P500 firms pointing to overall annual profit growth of almost 11% through the last quarter, stock futures were up smartly before the open. The S&P500 closed above the 6,000 mark on Tuesday for the first time this year - less than 1% from record highs. Despite the AI tilt, Trump continued to rattle the tariff sabre overnight - without necessarily giving much additional clarity on where exactly or when they may be coming. Trump vowed to hit the ""very, very bad"" European Union with tariffs and said his administration was also discussing a 10% punitive duty on Chinese imports - blaming the trafficking of fentanyl from China to the U.S. via Mexico and Canada. Currency gyrations around the threats seemed to have calmed down, however, with traders adopting a 'wait and see' mode and assuming any moves will happen only after the countries in question respond to Trump's main concerns. The dollar index slipped to its lowest in two weeks, with the euro clocking its best levels of the year so far - even as European Central Bank officials speaking in Davos lined up behind more interest rate cuts this year. Even though exchange rate swings have seemed large this week, implied currency volatility gauges have actually subsided. Three-month dollar/yen 'vol' fell to its lowest since July on Wednesday with the Bank of Japan's latest interest rate hike now seen to be baked in. Equivalent euro vol measures are the lowest since November, and even sterling measures have returned to two-week lows. European shares brushed off Trump's trade threats too, with the STOXX600 index hitting a record high on Wednesday. Addidas helped Germany's DAX to a new record too and the sportswear brand jumped 6% after its latest results. The near 6% gain in benchmark euro zone stock indexes this year is twice that of the S&P500 in dollar terms - with Bank of America's latest global fund manager claiming allocations to European stocks this month were their second largest allocation in a quarter of a century. Chinese stocks were less enthusiastic about being back in the tariff firing line, however, and fell back about 1% on Wednesday - the yuan slipping too. Despite the pre-inauguration phone call between Trump and Chinese President XI Jinping last week, Trump appears to be emboldened enough to publicly resume the trade war he started in his first term. Back in fixed income markets, the jittery start to the new year seems to have calmed considerably. A combination of lower oil prices - due in part to Trump's plans to increase domestic drilling - and the lack of immediate tariff hikes has helped to cosset Treasury yields back at levels seen at the turn of the year. After significant relief from U.S. inflation data last week, Canada underlined the optimism on consumer prices on Tuesday with an unexpectedly large drop in monthly prices that kept annual inflation below the Bank of Canada's 2% target last month. Elsewhere, recently agitated British gilts also outperformed this week as news of a big drop in UK hiring and robust auction demand for the bonds offset higher public borrowing numbers and pulled yields back to where they were at the start of the year. Key developments that should provide more direction to U.S. markets later on Tuesday: * Canada December producer price inflation * US corporate earnings: Halliburton, Procter & Gamble, Johnson & Johnson, Discover Financial, Kinder Morgan, Steel Dynamics, Abbott Laboratories, Travelers, Amphenol, Ge Vernova, TE Connectivity, Textron, Teledyne * World Economic Forum in Davos, including European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde, Bundesbank President Joachim Nagel, Bank of France chief Francois Villeroy de Galhau, Dutch central bank boss Klaas Knot and European Union commissioner Valdis Dombrovskis * German Chancellor Olaf Scholz meets French President Emmanuel Macron in Paris * US Treasury sells $13 billion of 20-year bonds (By Mike Dolan, editing by William Maclean; mike.dolan@thomsonreuters.com) Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(10, 23, 'DATE'), (27, 31, 'GPE'), (56, 66, 'PERSON'), (128, 132, 'GPE'), (143, 155, 'PERSON'), (229, 238, 'DATE'), (319, 324, 'PERSON'), (328, 335, 'DATE'), (377, 395, 'MONEY'), (551, 558, 'ORG'), (567, 573, 'ORG'), (575, 583, 'ORG'), (588, 594, 'ORG'), (623, 631, 'PRODUCT'), (682, 699, 'CARDINAL'), (708, 725, 'GPE'), (727, 735, 'ORG'), (750, 763, 'PERCENT'), (767, 772, 'GPE'), (788, 794, 'ORG'), (802, 804, 'PERCENT'), (812, 817, 'TIME'), (827, 836, 'DATE'), (889, 896, 'ORG'), (903, 906, 'PERCENT'), (936, 945, 'DATE'), (997, 1009, 'CARDINAL'), (1031, 1050, 'DATE'), (1114, 1120, 'ORG'), (1198, 1203, 'ORG'), (1221, 1228, 'DATE'), (1278, 1283, 'ORG'), (1316, 1322, 'ORG'), (1345, 1352, 'GPE'), (1440, 1449, 'DATE'), (1505, 1511, 'DATE'), (1529, 1539, 'PERCENT'), (1548, 1564, 'DATE'), (1641, 1646, 'CARDINAL'), (1655, 1662, 'DATE'), (1671, 1676, 'ORDINAL'), (1682, 1691, 'DATE'), (1694, 1706, 'PERCENT'), (1747, 1752, 'PERSON'), (1790, 1799, 'TIME'), (1898, 1903, 'PERSON'), (1938, 1952, 'ORG'), (2016, 2019, 'PERCENT'), (2037, 2044, 'NORP'), (2096, 2101, 'GPE'), (2109, 2113, 'GPE'), (2118, 2124, 'GPE'), (2129, 2135, 'GPE'), (2339, 2344, 'PERSON'), (2404, 2413, 'DATE'), (2457, 2465, 'DATE'), (2483, 2504, 'ORG'), (2527, 2532, 'GPE'), (2573, 2582, 'DATE'), (2635, 2644, 'DATE'), (2705, 2716, 'DATE'), (2759, 2763, 'DATE'), (2767, 2776, 'DATE'), (2782, 2801, 'ORG'), (2903, 2911, 'DATE'), (2957, 2965, 'DATE'), (2972, 2980, 'NORP'), (3000, 3005, 'PERSON'), (3076, 3085, 'DATE'), (3087, 3094, 'ORG'), (3102, 3109, 'GPE'), (3168, 3170, 'PERCENT'), (3206, 3208, 'PERCENT'), (3227, 3236, 'LOC'), (3251, 3260, 'DATE'), (3312, 3329, 'ORG'), (3381, 3389, 'NORP'), (3397, 3407, 'DATE'), (3419, 3425, 'ORDINAL'), (3448, 3470, 'DATE'), (3472, 3479, 'NORP'), (3583, 3585, 'PERCENT'), (3589, 3598, 'DATE'), (3672, 3677, 'PERSON'), (3682, 3689, 'NORP'), (3700, 3710, 'PERSON'), (3711, 3720, 'DATE'), (3722, 3727, 'PERSON'), (3811, 3816, 'ORDINAL'), (3874, 3886, 'DATE'), (3973, 3978, 'PERSON'), (4079, 4087, 'ORG'), (4118, 4138, 'DATE'), (4170, 4174, 'GPE'), (4190, 4199, 'DATE'), (4201, 4207, 'GPE'), (4254, 4261, 'DATE'), (4297, 4304, 'DATE'), (4322, 4328, 'DATE'), (4345, 4365, 'ORG'), (4366, 4368, 'PERCENT'), (4376, 4386, 'DATE'), (4417, 4424, 'NORP'), (4449, 4458, 'DATE'), (4484, 4486, 'GPE'), (4618, 4639, 'DATE'), (4696, 4700, 'GPE'), (4718, 4725, 'DATE'), (4729, 4735, 'GPE'), (4736, 4744, 'DATE'), (4772, 4774, 'GPE'), (4795, 4824, 'ORG'), (4826, 4843, 'ORG'), (4845, 4863, 'ORG'), (4865, 4878, 'ORG'), (4880, 4894, 'ORG'), (4896, 4915, 'ORG'), (4917, 4926, 'ORG'), (4928, 4936, 'ORG'), (4938, 4948, 'ORG'), (4950, 4965, 'ORG'), (4967, 4974, 'ORG'), (4976, 4984, 'ORG'), (4987, 5007, 'EVENT'), (5011, 5016, 'GPE'), (5028, 5049, 'ORG'), (5060, 5077, 'PERSON'), (5079, 5089, 'ORG'), (5100, 5113, 'PERSON'), (5115, 5129, 'ORG'), (5136, 5163, 'PERSON'), (5165, 5170, 'NORP'), (5189, 5199, 'PERSON'), (5204, 5218, 'ORG'), (5232, 5250, 'PERSON'), (5253, 5259, 'NORP'), (5271, 5282, 'PERSON'), (5289, 5295, 'NORP'), (5306, 5321, 'PERSON'), (5325, 5330, 'GPE'), (5333, 5344, 'ORG'), (5351, 5362, 'MONEY'), (5366, 5373, 'DATE'), (5384, 5394, 'PERSON'), (5407, 5422, 'PERSON')]}"
"In This Article: By Stephen Nellis and Krystal Hu (Reuters) - Microsoft (MSFT) on Tuesday said it has changed some key terms of a deal with OpenAI after the ChatGPT creator announced a joint venture with Oracle (ORCL) and Japan's SoftBank Group to build up to $500 billion of new AI data centers in the United States. President Donald Trump gathered the leaders of the ""Stargate"" effort at the White House on Tuesday to announce the deal, saying it was intended to help keep the United States ahead of China and other rivals in the global AI race, using chips from Nvidia (NVDA). Since 2019, Microsoft has had arrangements with OpenAI that gave the Redmond, Washington-based company the exclusive right to build new computing infrastructure for OpenAI. Microsoft, in a blog post, said it has ""approved OpenAI's ability to build additional capacity, primarily for research and training of models."" That opened the door for OpenAI to work with Oracle. A person familiar with the deal said that Stargate is a joint venture structured as new entity in which OpenAI has an equity stake, governance rights and operational control. It will have a separate board appointed by the founding members and its own CEO, this person said. The venture will also have other investors including United Arab Emirates firm MGX. Microsoft, along with Nvidia and Arm, will be a ""technology partner"" in the new venture, but is not listed as an equity funder. SoftBank CEO Masayoshi Son is will be the entity's board chairman, according to a statement from OpenAI posted on social media site X. But Microsoft said that it still retains the exclusive right to offer OpenAI's API - technology shorthand for application programming interface, which is the main way that software developers and business customers buy OpenAI's services. That means Oracle will not be able to host OpenAI's primary source of revenue. Oracle did not immediately respond to a request for comment on Microsoft's statements. Microsoft said it has ""revenue sharing agreements that flow both ways"" with OpenAI. ""The key elements of our partnership remain in place for the duration of our contract through 2030, with our access to OpenAI’s IP, our revenue sharing arrangements and our exclusivity on OpenAI’s APIs all continuing forward,"" Microsoft said. Microsoft also said ""OpenAI recently made a new, large Azure commitment that will continue to support all OpenAI products as well as training,"" referring to Microsoft's Azure cloud computing service. (Reporting by Stephen Nellis in San Francisco and Krystal Hu in Davos, Switzerland; Editing by Christopher Cushing) Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(20, 34, 'PERSON'), (39, 49, 'PERSON'), (51, 58, 'ORG'), (62, 71, 'ORG'), (73, 77, 'ORG'), (82, 89, 'DATE'), (140, 146, 'ORG'), (157, 164, 'PRODUCT'), (204, 210, 'ORG'), (212, 216, 'ORG'), (222, 227, 'GPE'), (230, 244, 'ORG'), (254, 272, 'MONEY'), (299, 316, 'GPE'), (328, 340, 'PERSON'), (370, 378, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (390, 405, 'FAC'), (409, 416, 'DATE'), (475, 492, 'GPE'), (502, 507, 'GPE'), (565, 571, 'ORG'), (573, 577, 'ORG'), (586, 590, 'DATE'), (592, 601, 'ORG'), (628, 634, 'ORG'), (649, 656, 'GPE'), (658, 668, 'GPE'), (745, 751, 'ORG'), (753, 762, 'ORG'), (802, 808, 'ORG'), (922, 928, 'ORG'), (942, 948, 'ORG'), (992, 1000, 'ORG'), (1054, 1060, 'ORG'), (1277, 1297, 'GPE'), (1303, 1306, 'ORG'), (1308, 1317, 'ORG'), (1330, 1336, 'ORG'), (1341, 1344, 'ORG'), (1436, 1444, 'ORG'), (1449, 1462, 'PERSON'), (1533, 1539, 'ORG'), (1575, 1584, 'ORG'), (1641, 1647, 'ORG'), (1790, 1796, 'ORG'), (1820, 1826, 'ORG'), (1852, 1858, 'ORG'), (1888, 1894, 'ORG'), (1951, 1960, 'ORG'), (1975, 1984, 'ORG'), (2051, 2057, 'ORG'), (2153, 2157, 'DATE'), (2178, 2184, 'ORG'), (2247, 2253, 'ORG'), (2286, 2295, 'ORG'), (2302, 2311, 'ORG'), (2323, 2329, 'ORG'), (2357, 2362, 'ORG'), (2408, 2414, 'ORG'), (2459, 2468, 'ORG'), (2471, 2476, 'PRODUCT'), (2516, 2530, 'PERSON'), (2534, 2547, 'GPE'), (2552, 2562, 'PERSON'), (2566, 2571, 'GPE'), (2573, 2584, 'GPE'), (2597, 2616, 'PERSON')]}"
"In This Article: A publicly traded coffee wholesaler has filed a breach-of-contract and negligence lawsuit against a Texas-based logistics company nearly a year after a load of coffee, valued at almost $84,500, went missing. Coffee Holding Co. (NASDAQ: JVA) of Staten Island, New York, a wholesale green coffee roaster and trading company, filed suit on Jan. 10 against Ryaan Logistics Group of Prosper, Texas, in the U.S. District Court for the Eastern District of New York. The suit claims that Ryaan Logistics brokered the load to Florida-based AFC Trucking. However, an investigation later determined that AFC Trucking’s identity and DOT number had been stolen and its information had been changed online, according to court documents. FreightWaves has reached out to Coffee Holding’s attorney, Allyn J. Crawford of Crawford & Desantis LLP of Staten Island, for comment. The complaint states that a different carrier, Maya Transportation, arrived on Feb. 16, 2024, at Coffee Holding’s La Junta, Colorado, facility to pick up the shipment. The lawsuit alleges the driver purporting to be with AFC Trucking used his phone to show Coffee Holding’s logistics staff the load number provided by Ryaan Logistics. The coffee was scheduled to be delivered three days later on Feb. 19 to United Natural Foods in Centralia, Washington. Court documents claim that a Ryaan Logistics employee emailed Coffee Holding’s logistics department on Feb. 20, a day after the load was to be delivered, stating that “the driver had missed his delivery appointment” and Ryaan had lost communication with the driver for the load. According to a business entity search on the Texas secretary of state’s database, Ryaan Logistics is owned by Rahul Minhas. The company’s common carrier authority was granted in March 2016, but its operating authority was involuntarily revoked in July 2022. Its broker authority was granted in August 2020 and remains active. FreightWaves reached out to Minhas of Ryaan Logistics for comment about the lawsuit. According to the suit, Ryaan Logistics contacted its insurance company about the missing load but didn’t immediately contact law enforcement. Ryaan Logistics claims that it later found out the name of the driver who purported to be with AFC Trucking. After sharing the name with Coffee Holding, the company requested that the La Junta Police Department run a background check on the driver, who allegedly had an extensive criminal record. According to court documents, Ryaan was able to track the load to two warehouses in California, but it was never found, despite Coffee Holding having filed an incident report on Feb. 22 with the La Junta police. In the suit, Coffee Holding claims that Ryaan Logistics breached its contract by failing to deliver the load. The company alleges it was never compensated by Ryaan Logistics for the missing shipment worth more than $84,000. Coffee Holding also claims the brokerage was negligent in vetting the carrier and “had a duty to ensure the driver who picked up the coffee load was in fact the trucking company it booked to transport the load,” according to court filings. The suit has been referred to U.S. Magistrate Judge Joseph A. Marutollo. An initial conference regarding the suit is scheduled for March 14. Do you have a news tip or story to share? Send Clarissa Hawes an email or message @cage_writer on X, formerly known as Twitter. Your name will not be used without your permission. Read more articles here: Wyoming trucking company pays $124,000 to settle sexual harassment suitNew Hampshire man created fake trucking, ag businesses to collect COVID fundsSt. Louis trucking company, affiliate file for Chapter 11 bankruptcy The post Caffeine fix? Coffee wholesaler sues brokerage over missing $84,500 load appeared first on FreightWaves. Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(117, 122, 'GPE'), (147, 160, 'DATE'), (195, 209, 'MONEY'), (225, 243, 'ORG'), (253, 256, 'ORG'), (261, 274, 'GPE'), (276, 284, 'GPE'), (354, 361, 'DATE'), (370, 391, 'ORG'), (395, 402, 'GPE'), (404, 409, 'GPE'), (418, 422, 'GPE'), (423, 437, 'ORG'), (446, 462, 'LOC'), (497, 512, 'ORG'), (534, 541, 'GPE'), (548, 560, 'ORG'), (610, 624, 'ORG'), (638, 641, 'ORG'), (740, 752, 'ORG'), (772, 788, 'ORG'), (799, 816, 'PERSON'), (820, 843, 'ORG'), (847, 860, 'GPE'), (922, 941, 'ORG'), (954, 967, 'DATE'), (972, 988, 'ORG'), (989, 997, 'GPE'), (999, 1007, 'GPE'), (1096, 1108, 'ORG'), (1132, 1148, 'ORG'), (1193, 1208, 'ORG'), (1251, 1267, 'DATE'), (1271, 1278, 'DATE'), (1282, 1302, 'ORG'), (1306, 1315, 'GPE'), (1317, 1327, 'GPE'), (1358, 1373, 'ORG'), (1391, 1407, 'ORG'), (1432, 1439, 'DATE'), (1441, 1446, 'DATE'), (1549, 1554, 'ORG'), (1653, 1658, 'GPE'), (1690, 1705, 'ORG'), (1718, 1730, 'PERSON'), (1786, 1796, 'DATE'), (1855, 1864, 'DATE'), (1902, 1913, 'DATE'), (1934, 1946, 'ORG'), (1962, 1968, 'PERSON'), (1972, 1987, 'ORG'), (2042, 2057, 'ORG'), (2161, 2176, 'ORG'), (2256, 2268, 'ORG'), (2298, 2312, 'ORG'), (2341, 2371, 'ORG'), (2488, 2493, 'ORG'), (2524, 2527, 'CARDINAL'), (2542, 2552, 'GPE'), (2586, 2600, 'ORG'), (2636, 2643, 'DATE'), (2653, 2661, 'GPE'), (2683, 2697, 'ORG'), (2710, 2725, 'ORG'), (2828, 2843, 'ORG'), (2875, 2892, 'MONEY'), (2894, 2908, 'ORG'), (3164, 3168, 'GPE'), (3186, 3205, 'PERSON'), (3265, 3273, 'DATE'), (3322, 3336, 'PERSON'), (3394, 3401, 'ORG'), (3480, 3487, 'GPE'), (3511, 3518, 'MONEY'), (3617, 3622, 'ORG'), (3630, 3637, 'GPE'), (3675, 3685, 'LAW'), (3767, 3773, 'MONEY'), (3797, 3809, 'ORG')]}"
"(Bloomberg) -- JPMorgan Chase & Co.’s dealmakers are spending their time in the Swiss Alps huddling with ebullient clients, but the boss of the biggest US bank is striking a more cautious tone. Most Read from Bloomberg Texas HOA Charged With Discrimination for Banning Section 8 Renters How Sanctuary Cities Are Preparing for Another Showdown With Trump Donations to LA Fire Victims Rise Past $200 Million Mark NY’s Hochul Calls for Law Banning Cell Phone Use in Schools LA Schools Wrecked by Fires Plead on GoFundMe for Help to Reopen “Asset prices are kind of inflated” in the US stock market, Chief Executive Officer Jamie Dimon said in a CNBC interview Wednesday from the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland. “You need fairly good outcomes to justify those prices, and we’re all hoping for that. I think having pro-growth strategies helps make that happen, but there are negatives out there and they can tend to surprise you.” His remarks came hours after Filippo Gori, the bank’s co-head of global banking, described a “sense of euphoria” among clients in an interview from the annual gathering. He added that the new administration “has clearly brought the animal spirits back to the market.” Daniel Pinto, JPMorgan’s outgoing president, said Wednesday on Bloomberg Television that the US economy is in a good place, though inflation and geopolitics could derail the optimism. The bankers’ remarks come on the third day of Donald Trump’s second presidential term, and Wall Street has embraced the return of Trump, who finance executives see as more business-friendly and growth-oriented than his predecessor. Dimon said after the election in November that many bankers were “dancing in the street.” The S&P 500 index has climbed 4.6% since Trump was elected. Dimon reiterated that he remains cautious about global deficit spending, the potential for persistent inflation and geopolitical issues. On deficits, he added that growth is “the only real solution” to reduce them. The longtime JPMorgan CEO said earlier this month that he wasn’t surprised that Trump won the US presidential election. In an interview from the World Economic Forum last year, Dimon said that Trump was “kind of right” on some issues. “I was really just trying to make the point of, respect the voter,” Dimon said Wednesday of his remarks last year. “The problem with putting a voter in a box is a voter may be voting for some completely different reasons than you think or I think or something like that, and respect why they may have grievances or angers.” In the wide-ranging interview, Dimon also touched on billionaire Elon Musk and the government-efficiency effort he’s set to run. Dimon said he and Musk have “settled some of our differences” and he wishes the panel the best. “I think it is completely rational for someone to look at our government and say it’s been ineffective,” Dimon said. “Government needs to be more accountable, it needs to be more efficient, it should be outcomes-based.” JPMorgan shuffled its top ranks last week, less than a year after its last major shakeup. Pinto, who has been president and chief operating officer of the firm for about three years, will retire at the end of next year. Longtime executive Jenn Piepszak was named Pinto’s replacement as COO, though she ruled herself out as a potential successor to Dimon when he eventually retires. That put the spotlight on three executives: Marianne Lake, who runs the firm’s consumer arm, and commercial and investment bank co-heads Troy Rohrbaugh and Doug Petno. Dimon has been CEO of JPMorgan for almost 20 years, and the succession question has long been a hot topic on Wall Street. Dimon said last week that his base case is to stay a few more years. “Daniel leaving leaves a vacuum, but that’s good because now other people have filled that vacuum,” Dimon said Wednesday. Pinto said Wednesday that it’s the right time to embrace the new generation at JPMorgan. He also said he feels good about his firm’s ability to compete with private credit, which has boomed in recent years, but that the sector’s financing of smaller businesses warrants attention. “There is a lot of direct lending going into the smaller side of middle markets,” Pinto said. “How these funds are going to behave in a downturn with small businesses is something you want to be concerned about it, you want to keep an eye on.” --With assistance from Jan-Henrik Förster and Dinesh Nair. Most Read from Bloomberg Businessweek How Kendrick Lamar Turned Beef With Drake Into Music Superstardom Walgreens Replaced Fridge Doors With Smart Screens. It’s Now a $200 Million Fiasco Elon Musk’s Inaugural Highs (and Lows) Giant Batteries Are Transforming the World’s Electrical Grids Greek Police Say Eggs Were Stolen from IVF Clinic Patients ©2025 Bloomberg L.P. Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(1, 10, 'ORG'), (15, 37, 'ORG'), (76, 90, 'LOC'), (152, 154, 'GPE'), (209, 218, 'ORG'), (219, 224, 'GPE'), (348, 353, 'PERSON'), (367, 369, 'GPE'), (393, 405, 'MONEY'), (411, 413, 'GPE'), (416, 422, 'ORG'), (471, 473, 'GPE'), (579, 581, 'GPE'), (620, 631, 'PERSON'), (642, 646, 'ORG'), (657, 666, 'DATE'), (672, 696, 'FAC'), (700, 705, 'GPE'), (707, 718, 'GPE'), (955, 960, 'TIME'), (967, 979, 'PERSON'), (1090, 1096, 'DATE'), (1206, 1218, 'PERSON'), (1220, 1228, 'ORG'), (1256, 1265, 'DATE'), (1269, 1289, 'ORG'), (1299, 1301, 'GPE'), (1419, 1432, 'DATE'), (1436, 1450, 'PERSON'), (1451, 1457, 'ORDINAL'), (1520, 1525, 'PERSON'), (1622, 1627, 'PERSON'), (1655, 1663, 'DATE'), (1742, 1746, 'PERCENT'), (1753, 1758, 'PERSON'), (1772, 1777, 'PERSON'), (2000, 2008, 'ORG'), (2018, 2036, 'DATE'), (2067, 2072, 'PERSON'), (2081, 2083, 'GPE'), (2128, 2152, 'ORG'), (2153, 2162, 'DATE'), (2164, 2169, 'PERSON'), (2180, 2185, 'PERSON'), (2290, 2295, 'PERSON'), (2301, 2310, 'DATE'), (2326, 2335, 'DATE'), (2577, 2582, 'PERSON'), (2611, 2620, 'PERSON'), (2675, 2680, 'PERSON'), (2693, 2697, 'PERSON'), (2876, 2881, 'PERSON'), (2991, 2999, 'ORG'), (3023, 3032, 'DATE'), (3034, 3050, 'DATE'), (3081, 3086, 'PERSON'), (3155, 3172, 'DATE'), (3189, 3209, 'DATE'), (3230, 3243, 'PERSON'), (3254, 3259, 'PERSON'), (3339, 3344, 'PERSON'), (3399, 3404, 'CARDINAL'), (3417, 3430, 'PERSON'), (3510, 3524, 'PERSON'), (3529, 3539, 'PERSON'), (3541, 3546, 'PERSON'), (3563, 3571, 'ORG'), (3576, 3591, 'DATE'), (3663, 3668, 'PERSON'), (3674, 3683, 'DATE'), (3714, 3730, 'DATE'), (3733, 3739, 'PERSON'), (3832, 3837, 'PERSON'), (3843, 3852, 'DATE'), (3854, 3859, 'PERSON'), (3865, 3874, 'DATE'), (3933, 3941, 'ORG'), (4047, 4059, 'DATE'), (4217, 4222, 'PERSON'), (4402, 4420, 'PERSON'), (4425, 4436, 'PERSON'), (4453, 4475, 'ORG'), (4480, 4494, 'PERSON'), (4512, 4517, 'PERSON'), (4542, 4551, 'ORG'), (4605, 4617, 'MONEY'), (4625, 4636, 'PERSON'), (4726, 4731, 'NORP'), (4765, 4775, 'ORG'), (4791, 4805, 'ORG')]}"
"In This Article: (Reuters) - Goldman Sachs CEO David Solomon said on Wednesday it was important for the U.S. and China, the world's two largest economic superpowers, to improve their bilateral ties. His comments during an interview to CNBC at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, come just days after Donald Trump became U.S. President and threatened to deliver fresh tariffs against imports from China and the European Union. In his last term as president, Trump had heaped tariffs on more than $300 billion of Chinese imports. Solomon said the rebalancing of certain trade agreements could be constructive for U.S. growth if it is handled right. ""The question is, how far? How quickly, how thoughtfully?"" he told CNBC. Goldman Sachs has a long history of presence in China with offices in Beijing, Shanghai and Shenzhen. In 2021, the investment bank received an approval from China's securities regulator to take full control of its mainland securities business. Solomon also reiterated that he expects to see a meaningful increase in deal activity in 2025. Last month, he told a Reuters conference that dealmaking in equities could surpass the 10-year averages this year. (Reporting by Arasu Kannagi Basil in Bengaluru and Saeed Azhar in New York; Editing by Arun Koyyur) Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(18, 25, 'ORG'), (29, 42, 'ORG'), (47, 60, 'PERSON'), (69, 78, 'DATE'), (104, 108, 'GPE'), (113, 118, 'GPE'), (132, 135, 'CARDINAL'), (235, 239, 'ORG'), (243, 267, 'EVENT'), (271, 276, 'GPE'), (278, 289, 'GPE'), (296, 305, 'DATE'), (312, 324, 'PERSON'), (332, 336, 'GPE'), (408, 413, 'GPE'), (418, 436, 'ORG'), (469, 474, 'PERSON'), (497, 519, 'MONEY'), (523, 530, 'NORP'), (540, 547, 'PERSON'), (623, 627, 'GPE'), (726, 730, 'ORG'), (732, 745, 'ORG'), (780, 785, 'GPE'), (802, 809, 'GPE'), (811, 819, 'GPE'), (824, 832, 'GPE'), (837, 841, 'DATE'), (889, 894, 'GPE'), (976, 983, 'PERSON'), (1065, 1069, 'DATE'), (1071, 1081, 'DATE'), (1093, 1100, 'ORG'), (1158, 1165, 'DATE'), (1175, 1184, 'DATE'), (1200, 1219, 'PERSON'), (1223, 1232, 'GPE'), (1237, 1248, 'PERSON'), (1252, 1260, 'GPE'), (1273, 1284, 'PERSON')]}"
"In This Article: DUBAI (Reuters) - Abu Dhabi-listed cryptomining and blockchain conglomerate Phoenix Group has struck an 80-megawatt (MW) power purchase agreement (PPA) in Ethiopia, it said on Wednesday, as it pursues a global diversification strategy by entering the Africa market. Under the deal, Ethiopian Electric Power (EEP) will provide the energy needed to support Phoenix's bitcoin mining expansion, with supplies due to start in the second quarter. The firm did not provide details on the location of the facility or the size of the deal, which was signed in partnership with Abu Dhabi cybersecurity firm Data7, it said in a statement. ""We are aggressively building out our mining capabilities,"" Phoenix CEO Munaf Ali said, adding the additional capacity would fuel further growth as the company prepares for a dual-listing on Nasdaq. The company ""is actively engaged in discussions with financial institutions and NASDAQ to evaluate the most effective way forward"", it said in a separate statement to Reuters, without providing a timeline for the listing. Phoenix, which counts Abu Dhabi's largest listed firm IHC among its shareholders, operates multiple mining facilities in countries including the UAE, the U.S. and Canada. IHC, which is chaired by Sheikh Tahnoon bin Zayed Al Nahyan, the UAE's national security adviser and a brother of UAE President Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed, has a sprawling portfolio of investments that ranges from agriculture to energy and includes a cryptomining firm. In Africa, Phoenix is exploring more opportunities in Ethiopia, and assessing other regions ""with strong energy prospects,"" it said in the statement to Reuters. It is also exploring opportunities to enter the South American market and looking at Brazil, it added. (Reporting by Federico Maccioni. Editing by Mark Potter) Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(17, 22, 'GPE'), (35, 44, 'GPE'), (93, 106, 'ORG'), (121, 132, 'QUANTITY'), (172, 180, 'GPE'), (193, 202, 'DATE'), (268, 274, 'LOC'), (299, 323, 'ORG'), (325, 328, 'ORG'), (372, 379, 'ORG'), (438, 456, 'DATE'), (585, 594, 'GPE'), (614, 619, 'ORG'), (705, 712, 'ORG'), (717, 726, 'PERSON'), (924, 930, 'ORG'), (1011, 1018, 'ORG'), (1066, 1073, 'ORG'), (1088, 1099, 'GPE'), (1120, 1123, 'ORG'), (1211, 1214, 'GPE'), (1220, 1224, 'GPE'), (1229, 1235, 'GPE'), (1237, 1240, 'ORG'), (1269, 1296, 'PERSON'), (1302, 1305, 'GPE'), (1351, 1354, 'GPE'), (1372, 1390, 'PERSON'), (1509, 1515, 'LOC'), (1517, 1524, 'ORG'), (1560, 1568, 'GPE'), (1658, 1665, 'ORG'), (1715, 1729, 'NORP'), (1752, 1758, 'GPE'), (1784, 1801, 'PERSON'), (1814, 1825, 'PERSON')]}"
"In This Article: A new SEC cryptocurrency task force announced on Donald Trump's second day in office helped stoke some new investor enthusiasm for digital assets as the crypto world waited for executive orders from the new president. The goal of the ""crypto task force"" from the Securities and Exchange Commission is to help the US regulator ""draw clear regulatory lines, provide realistic paths to registration, craft sensible disclosure frameworks, and deploy enforcement resources judiciously,"" according to the SEC. The price of bitcoin (BTC-USD), the world's largest cryptocurrency, rose Tuesday back above $106,000 after sliding Monday following Trump's inauguration. The SEC clashed repeatedly with some of the biggest players in the crypto world during Joe Biden's time in office. Trump promised to replace Biden's SEC boss Gary Gensler with someone more favorable to the industry. His choice, Paul Atkins, is still seeking confirmation in the Senate, and SEC Commissioner Mark Uyeda is running the agency as acting chair. Industry executives are testing Trump's new SEC with fresh applications this week for exchange-traded funds that, if approved, would give investors even more exposure to various crypto assets. On Tuesday, Rex Shares and Osprey Funds jointly filed seven different applications to launch crypto-related ETFs, including those holding shares of XRP, SOL, Dogecoin (DOGE), and the president's official memecoin (TRUMP). Last year, the SEC allowed BlackRock and other giant money managers to launch spot bitcoin ETFs. ""We are most definitely anticipating a more welcoming approach from the SEC, and you will see more product filings from us,"" said Matthew Sigel, head of digital assets research for asset manager VanEck, one among the managers allowed to issue spot bitcoin ETFs in 2024. One slight disappointment for the industry so far this week is that Trump — who in 2024 pledged to make the United States the ""crypto capital of the planet"" — ended his first day in office without mentioning crypto or releasing any executive orders targeted at the industry. Many in the industry still expect those orders to happen. ""The market is absolutely disappointed that there was no activity with regard to crypto yesterday,"" Dan Hughes, chief technology officer and founder for crypto startup Radix, said in emailed comments. ""Any executive order targeted positively towards crypto, even if minor, would turn the tide pretty fast,"" Hughes added. One immediate action the new president could have taken is repealing Biden’s own March 2022 executive order on crypto assets, which urged regulators to ""take strong steps to reduce the risks that digital assets could pose."" ""I feel a little disappointed that was not repealed, along with the 80 executive orders that were,"" said Sigel of VanEck. ""The longer that there's no executive order regarding this asset class, the more impatient the market is likely to get, but I do think that [the Trump administration] bought themselves some time with rhetoric,"" Sigel added. One crucial rule that many in the crypto and banking industry hope to see repealed is a piece of accounting guidance from the SEC that virtually stops banks from holding crypto in custody for clients. Much of what Trump has promised the crypto world can be fulfilled with personnel changes. And the incoming administration has already named three pro-crypto regulators as acting heads of regulatory agencies. On Tuesday, FDIC acting chairman Travis Hill published a list of priorities for the bank regulatory agency under his watch. One included more transparency in how the agency approaches digital assets. The Commodities and Futures Trading Commission also named one of its crypto-friendlier commissioners, Caroline Pham, as its acting chair on Monday. Pham, a Biden nominee and former Citigroup banker, supported clearer regulation for digital assets as well as granting the CFTC more oversight in policing the market. Many in the crypto industry are willing to wait longer for more substantive changes. Leonard Lancia, CEO of crypto market maker Portofino Technologies, said, ""for the crypto market, the potential for a significant and well-thought-out Executive Order (EO) remains an exciting opportunity."" One regional bank boss, Fifth Third CEO Tim Spence, told Yahoo Finance that as overall regulatory rules for crypto become clearer, stablecoins are an area Fifth Third Bank ""certainly would contemplate playing in."" One of the biggest players in the crypto industry, Coinbase (COIN) CEO Brian Armstrong, told Yahoo Finance Tuesday that he is convinced Trump ""really wants to be the first bitcoin president."" Armstrong met with Trump prior to and after the election to advocate for the crypto industry. He said Trump is ""excited"" about the idea of a strategic bitcoin reserve. Senator Cynthia Lummis (R-Wyo.) is leading the efforts in Congress to create such a reserve. ""Any government that holds gold should also hold bitcoin as a reserve,"" he said, noting, ""If the US gets a strategic bitcoin reserve, probably the rest of the G20 will follow, or many of them, and that's just going to drive the bitcoin prices way up."" David Hollerith is a senior reporter for Yahoo Finance covering banking, crypto, and other areas in finance. Click here for in-depth analysis of the latest stock market news and events moving stock prices. Read the latest financial and business news from Yahoo Finance Correction: A previous version of this article misspelled Leonard Lancia's name. We regret the error. Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(23, 26, 'ORG'), (66, 80, 'PERSON'), (81, 91, 'DATE'), (276, 314, 'ORG'), (330, 332, 'GPE'), (516, 519, 'ORG'), (594, 601, 'DATE'), (614, 621, 'MONEY'), (636, 642, 'DATE'), (653, 658, 'PERSON'), (679, 682, 'ORG'), (762, 773, 'PERSON'), (790, 795, 'PERSON'), (816, 821, 'PERSON'), (824, 827, 'ORG'), (833, 845, 'PERSON'), (903, 914, 'PERSON'), (953, 959, 'ORG'), (965, 968, 'ORG'), (982, 992, 'PERSON'), (1064, 1069, 'PERSON'), (1076, 1079, 'ORG'), (1104, 1113, 'DATE'), (1228, 1235, 'DATE'), (1237, 1247, 'ORG'), (1252, 1264, 'ORG'), (1279, 1284, 'CARDINAL'), (1378, 1381, 'ORG'), (1383, 1391, 'ORG'), (1447, 1456, 'DATE'), (1462, 1465, 'ORG'), (1474, 1483, 'ORG'), (1616, 1619, 'ORG'), (1674, 1687, 'PERSON'), (1739, 1745, 'ORG'), (1808, 1812, 'DATE'), (1814, 1817, 'CARDINAL'), (1864, 1873, 'DATE'), (1882, 1887, 'PERSON'), (1897, 1901, 'DATE'), (1918, 1935, 'GPE'), (1979, 1992, 'DATE'), (2235, 2244, 'DATE'), (2247, 2257, 'PERSON'), (2315, 2320, 'ORG'), (2454, 2460, 'PERSON'), (2468, 2471, 'CARDINAL'), (2537, 2542, 'PERSON'), (2549, 2559, 'DATE'), (2760, 2762, 'CARDINAL'), (2797, 2802, 'PERSON'), (2806, 2812, 'ORG'), (2959, 2964, 'PERSON'), (3025, 3030, 'PERSON'), (3038, 3041, 'CARDINAL'), (3164, 3167, 'ORG'), (3252, 3257, 'PERSON'), (3379, 3384, 'CARDINAL'), (3450, 3457, 'DATE'), (3459, 3463, 'ORG'), (3480, 3491, 'PERSON'), (3571, 3574, 'CARDINAL'), (3647, 3693, 'ORG'), (3705, 3708, 'CARDINAL'), (3749, 3762, 'PERSON'), (3787, 3793, 'DATE'), (3795, 3799, 'PERSON'), (3803, 3808, 'PERSON'), (3828, 3837, 'ORG'), (3918, 3922, 'ORG'), (4047, 4061, 'PERSON'), (4090, 4112, 'ORG'), (4197, 4212, 'LAW'), (4252, 4255, 'CARDINAL'), (4276, 4287, 'ORG'), (4292, 4302, 'PERSON'), (4309, 4322, 'ORG'), (4407, 4423, 'ORG'), (4466, 4469, 'CARDINAL'), (4517, 4525, 'ORG'), (4527, 4531, 'ORG'), (4537, 4552, 'PERSON'), (4559, 4572, 'ORG'), (4573, 4580, 'DATE'), (4602, 4607, 'PERSON'), (4632, 4637, 'ORDINAL'), (4658, 4667, 'PERSON'), (4677, 4682, 'PERSON'), (4760, 4765, 'PERSON'), (4834, 4848, 'PERSON'), (4850, 4851, 'NORP'), (4852, 4856, 'GPE'), (4884, 4892, 'ORG'), (5016, 5018, 'GPE'), (5078, 5081, 'ORG'), (5171, 5186, 'PERSON'), (5212, 5225, 'ORG'), (5426, 5439, 'ORG'), (5498, 5514, 'PERSON')]}"
"In This Article: Johnson & Johnson (JNJ) beat on fourth quarter and full-year 2024 results, but its stock traded down on Wednesday morning to about $143 per share. Several negative impacts were highlighted in the look-back and look-ahead on an earnings call, despite the company beating Wall Street expectations on revenue by $70 million and reporting results on earnings per share in line with estimates. J&J reported total sales of $88.8 billion for 2024, up 4.3% compared to 2023. That includes slowing COVID-19 vaccine sales — a theme other vaccine makers are expected to see with a slower start to the respiratory virus season this year. The company reported earnings per share of $5.79 for 2024, up 11% year over year. Meanwhile, fourth quarter earnings were mixed, with $22 billion in sales, up 5.3% year over year, and earnings per share down 17% from the prior year at $1.41. But the good news is somewhat tempered by the ongoing talc case, which has weighed on its growth potential. A lawsuit in Texas is set to begin hearings on Feb. 18 and last up to a month thereafter. ""From there, the company anticipates the plaintiff lawyers to appeal this decision (if positive) to the 5th circuit in Texas, which was noted as being potentially more favorable on the requirement of bankruptcy (with the added difference of this being a pre-packaged bankruptcy),"" JPMorgan analysts wrote in a recent note to clients. Ahead of earnings, Bank of America Securities analysts lowered their price target for the company for 2025 from $166 per share to $160 over ongoing concerns from the talc lawsuit. In addition to the lawsuit, J&J anticipates some negative impact from foreign exchange for the year as well as slower medical device sales, with China's slowdown in procedures weighing on the company's potential revenues. The company is transitioning into a competitive market, as generics launch for its blockbuster anti-inflammatory arthritis drug Stelara. The drug is also now facing pricing pressures from a newly negotiated price with Medicare, one of its largest customer bases. Meanwhile, its growth in the fourth quarter came from its multiple myeloma drug, Darzalex, and several cancer drugs. The combined sales of the top six drugs totaled roughly $4.5 billion, or about 20% of revenues for the quarter. The big deal J&J announced it would acquire mental health disorder drugmaker Intra-Cellular (ITCI) for $14.6 billion at the annual JPMorgan Healthcare conference earlier this month. The company boasted cash flow of $20 billion for the full year last year, up $1.6 billion from 2023. Intra-Cellular has a drug, Caplyta, that J&J expects to capitalize on for newly approved mental health disorders in the near future. But the company largely expects the deal to be financed through debt. ""We plan to finance mainly with debt. We are not planning for material near-term cost synergies. Rather, we expect to accelerate penetration of Caplyta in existing markets, explore additional geographies to commercialize the portfolio, potentially accelerate research and development to expand into new indications,"" CFO Joe Wolk said on an earnings call. Experts believe that though Intra-Cellular was a large deal and set the baseline for M&A in biotech for the year, J&J isn't through. It has been slowly acquiring smaller biotechs in recent years. ""Company has capacity to add to either Pharma or Medtech and has been very acquisitive over the past several years in both spaces. Net debt now stands around $12bn which will be paid down with FCF over the next several quarters. Did not get sense business development done,"" Mizuho's healthcare expert Jared Holz wrote in a note to clients Wednesday. CEO Joaquin Duato hinted as much on the earnings call. ""External innovation has always been a very important part of our capital allocation strategy for Johnson and Johnson ... and in fact, we are one of the top investors not only in M&A but also in R&D. We are always looking for opportunities to be able to enhance our portfolio and our pipeline,"" Duato said. BofA analysts said in a recent report that J&J spends about 17% of its revenue on R&D, slightly lower than its US peer group average of 19%. Anjalee Khemlani is the senior health reporter at Yahoo Finance, covering all things pharma, insurance, care services, digital health, PBMs, and health policy and politics. That includes GLP-1s, of course. Follow Anjalee on social media platforms X (Twitter), LinkedIn Bluesky @AnjKhem. Click here for in-depth analysis of the latest health industry news and events impacting stock prices. Recommended Stories Sign in to access your portfolio","{'entities': [(17, 34, 'ORG'), (36, 39, 'ORG'), (49, 63, 'DATE'), (68, 77, 'DATE'), (78, 82, 'DATE'), (121, 130, 'DATE'), (131, 138, 'TIME'), (142, 152, 'MONEY'), (326, 337, 'MONEY'), (406, 409, 'ORG'), (434, 447, 'MONEY'), (452, 456, 'DATE'), (461, 465, 'PERCENT'), (478, 482, 'DATE'), (603, 631, 'DATE'), (632, 641, 'DATE'), (687, 691, 'MONEY'), (696, 700, 'DATE'), (705, 708, 'PERCENT'), (709, 723, 'DATE'), (736, 750, 'DATE'), (777, 788, 'MONEY'), (802, 806, 'PERCENT'), (807, 821, 'DATE'), (851, 854, 'PERCENT'), (860, 874, 'DATE'), (879, 883, 'MONEY'), (1006, 1011, 'GPE'), (1040, 1047, 'DATE'), (1057, 1070, 'DATE'), (1187, 1190, 'ORDINAL'), (1202, 1207, 'GPE'), (1364, 1372, 'ORG'), (1436, 1462, 'ORG'), (1519, 1523, 'DATE'), (1530, 1533, 'MONEY'), (1548, 1551, 'MONEY'), (1625, 1628, 'ORG'), (1688, 1696, 'DATE'), (1742, 1747, 'GPE'), (1947, 1954, 'PRODUCT'), (2037, 2045, 'ORG'), (2047, 2050, 'CARDINAL'), (2107, 2125, 'DATE'), (2163, 2171, 'PRODUCT'), (2229, 2232, 'CARDINAL'), (2247, 2267, 'MONEY'), (2272, 2281, 'PERCENT'), (2298, 2309, 'DATE'), (2324, 2327, 'ORG'), (2388, 2402, 'ORG'), (2404, 2408, 'ORG'), (2414, 2427, 'MONEY'), (2442, 2461, 'ORG'), (2473, 2491, 'DATE'), (2526, 2537, 'MONEY'), (2542, 2565, 'DATE'), (2570, 2582, 'MONEY'), (2588, 2592, 'DATE'), (2594, 2608, 'ORG'), (2621, 2628, 'PRODUCT'), (2635, 2638, 'ORG'), (2941, 2948, 'PRODUCT'), (3118, 3126, 'PERSON'), (3181, 3195, 'ORG'), (3257, 3265, 'DATE'), (3267, 3270, 'ORG'), (3335, 3347, 'DATE'), (3388, 3394, 'ORG'), (3398, 3405, 'ORG'), (3441, 3463, 'DATE'), (3500, 3523, 'MONEY'), (3551, 3576, 'DATE'), (3624, 3630, 'ORG'), (3651, 3661, 'PERSON'), (3689, 3698, 'DATE'), (3704, 3717, 'PERSON'), (3853, 3872, 'ORG'), (4050, 4055, 'PERSON'), (4062, 4066, 'ORG'), (4105, 4108, 'ORG'), (4116, 4125, 'PERCENT'), (4173, 4175, 'GPE'), (4198, 4201, 'PERCENT'), (4203, 4219, 'PERSON'), (4253, 4266, 'ORG'), (4416, 4423, 'PERSON'), (4463, 4471, 'ORG')]}"
